Kevin Washington

WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Web developer specialized in developing interfaces focused on user experience. I have experience with several programming languages and frameworks for web / mobile development and design. At the moment, I am a member of the Scientific Computing and Visualization Laboratory at the Federal University of Alagoas (LCCV / UFAL).

Computer Engineering student (UFAL), drone pilot and information security enthusiast - I also plant grapefruits and train pigeons in my spare time. Creator of COVID-19 AL dashboard.

Employment History

Developer, LCCV/UFAL, Maceió/AL

AUGUST 2019 - PRESENT

Developer and researcher with emphasis on well engineering.

Front-end Developer, AVNIDA, Maceió/AL

JUNE 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Front-end developer of the AVNIDA ad portal.

Developer, MTur - UFAL /CNPq - IFAL

2015 - 2019

Developer of educational mobile applications (Android/UWP) and for accessible tourism (Android/iOS) in projects financed by the Brazilian Ministry of Tourism and CNPq.

Education

Bachelor's degree in progress, Federal University of Alagoas (UFAL), Maceió/AL

JULY 2017 - PRESENT

Currently studying the sixth period of the bachelor's degree in computer engineering

Technician, Federal Institute of Alagoas (IFAL), Arapiraca/AL

JANUARY 2013 - JANUARY 2017

Computer Technician

Courses

Vue.js developer, .NET developer, Front-end engineer, UX designer and Code versioning with Git, ALURA

2018

Awards

HackaFlag Winner, Maceió/AL

2017

Winner of the Maceió stage of HackaFlag, the largest CTF in Latin America.

Details

Maceió/AL +55 82 98221-4242 kevin@kevinws.com

Links

GitHub

LinkedIn

Personal website

Skills

Angular, Node and Vue

HTML5, CSS3 and JS

Git, GitHub and GitLab

LESS and SASS

Graphic design and UX design

Eslint and JSLint

Jasmine and Karma

React

Django, Laravel and Rails

Ionic and Xamarin

Firebase and Digital Ocean

Languages

Portuguese

English